A Guide to the Confederate Pension Records, 1884-1978
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Certificates, 1908-1974., Extent: 39 boxes. (Box 27-66.)
  - Subseries A: Allowed, 1925-1974., Extent: 38 boxes. (Box 27-65.)
    - Sub Subseries 3: Widows, 1927-1974, 22 boxes. (Box 45-65)
      - 1949
        - Rappahannock-Wythe (Box 60, Folder 10)
        - Alexandria-Washington, D.C. (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - 1950
        - Accomack-Franklin (Box 61, Folder 2)
        - Giles-Nottoway (Box 61, Folder 3)
        - Orange-Surry (Box 61, Folder 4)
        - Tazewell-Wythe (Box 61, Folder 5)
        - Alexandria-Washington, D.C. (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - 1951
        - Accomack-Franklin (Box 62, Folder 1)
        - Giles-Patrick (Box 62, Folder 2)
        - Pittsylvania-Wythe (Box 62, Folder 3)
        - Alexandria-Washington, D.C. (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - 1952
        - Accomack-Greensville (Box 62, Folder 5)
        - Halifax-Pulaski (Box 62, Folder 6)
        - Rappahannock-Wythe (Box 62, Folder 7)
        - Alexandria-Washington, D.C. (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - 1953
        - Accomack-Henrico (Box 63, Folder 2)
        - Henry-Russell (Box 63, Folder 3)
        - Scott-Wythe (Box 63, Folder 4)
        - Alexandria-Washington, D.C. (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - 1954
        - Accomack-Highland (Box 63, Folder 6)
        - Isle of Wight-Russell (Box 63, Folder 7)
        - Scott-Wythe (Box 64, Folder 1)
        - Alexandria-Washington, D.C. (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - 1955
        - Accomack-Louisa (Box 64, Folder 3)
        - Madison-Wythe (Box 64, Folder 4)
        - Alexandria-Washington, D.C. (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - 1955
        - Accomack-Louisa (Box 64, Folder 3)
        - Madison-Wythe (Box 64, Folder 4)
        - Alexandria-Washington, D.C. (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - 1956
        - Accomack-Pulaski (Box 64, Folder 6)
        - Rappahannock-Wythe (Box 64, Folder 7)
        - Bristol-Washington, D.C. (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - 1957
        - Albemarle-Pulaski (Box 65, Folder 1)
        - Rappahannock-Wythe (Box 65, Folder 2)
        - Bristol-Washington, D.C. (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - 1958
        - Albemarle-Russell (Box 65, Folder 4)
        - Scott-Wythe (Box 65, Folder 5)
        - Bristol-Washington, D.C. (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - 1959-1960
      - 1969-1974
  - Subseries B: Disallowed, 1908-1929., Extent: 1 box. (Box 66.)
    The Disallowed Certificates subseries is housed in one archival box and is arranged alphabetically by locality, then chronologically with cities to the rear. This series contains both soldier and widow certificates and correspondence. The correspondence in this subseries is to/from John H. Johnson, Pension Clerk. Johnson's letters often provide reasons for the disallowance including the death of the pensioner, duplicate pension, rerated pension, paid pension, pensioner in Soldier's Home or asylum, out-of-state residency, and absence from pension roll.
    - Accomack-Grayson (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Halifax-Russell (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Scott-Wythe (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Alexandria-Washington, D.C. (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Series IV: Confederate Memorial Association, 1946-1974., Extent: 13 boxes. (Box 67-77.)
  The Confederate Memorial Association series is housed in thirteen archival boxes and is arranged in alphabetical order. Included are appropriations, correspondence, invoices, and reports of expenses. This series generally documents expenditures of Confederate Memorial Associations for the care and upkeep of the graves of Confederate soldiers in cemeteries throughout Virginia. Originally established an Act of Assembly in 1902, the Confederate Memorial Fund was created for the auditor of public accounts to annually draw a warrant upon the treasurer in favor of the treasurers of Confederate Memorial Associations.
  The appropriations file contains legislation regarding appropriations to aid Confederate Memorial Associations and organizations of the United Daughters of the Confederacy in Virginia to be used in caring for Confederate cemeteries and graves of Confederate soldiers and sailors. The Invoices document expenditures of funds by treasurers of various chapters of the United Daughters of the Confederacy to the Department of Accounts. The invoices include annual reports of Confederate Memorial Funds by U.D.C. chapters. These reports contain similar information provided in Reports of Expenses, but are later in date. The Reports of Expenses are arranged in chronological order, then alphabetically by locality, chapter, or cemetery. The reports document payments to individuals for the upkeep of Confederate graves, landscaping, fence repair, flag markers, grave markers, etc. The reports often include correspondence from treasurers of various chapters of the United Daughters of the Confederacy, Chief Pension Clerk John H. Johnson, Henry G. Gilmer & Sidney C. Day, Jr., comptrollers, and the treasurer of the Confederate Memorial Association. The report provides the amount of balance on hand, the amount of appropriation by the Commonwealth for the year, a list of disbursements including date of payment, to whom paid, on what account paid, and the amount paid. Each report is certified & signed by the commissioner in chancery. Note that numerous checks & receipts documenting the disbursements have been weeded from the collection since the information they provide is documented in the report.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Appropriation Requests, 1968-1969. (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Appropriations
    - 1968-1970 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Confederate Memorial Committees, 1960-1971. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Invoices
    - 1964-1966
      - Accomack (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Albemarle (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Alleghany (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Amelia (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Appomattox (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Botetourt (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Charlotte (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Craig (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Dinwiddie (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Fairfax (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Fauquier (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Floyd (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Giles (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Goochland (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Grayson (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - Greene (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - Hanover (Box 67, Folder 21)
      - Isle of Wight (Box 67, Folder 22)
      - King William (Box 67, Folder 23)
      - Lancaster (Box 67, Folder 24)
      - Lee (Box 67, Folder 25)
      - Loudoun (Box 67, Folder 26)
      - Madison (Box 67, Folder 27)
      - Mecklenburg (Box 67, Folder 28)
      - Montgomery (Box 67, Folder 29)
      - Nelson (Box 67, Folder 30)
      - Northumberland (Box 67, Folder 31)
      - Nottoway (Box 67, Folder 32)
      - Patrick (Box 67, Folder 33)
      - Pittsylvania (Box 67, Folder 34)
      - Powhatan (Box 67, Folder 35)
      - Prince Edward (Box 67, Folder 36)
      - Prince George (Box 67, Folder 37)
      - Prince William (Box 67, Folder 38)
      - Pulaski (Box 67, Folder 39)
      - Scott (Box 67a, Folder 1)
      - Shenandoah (Box 67a, Folder 2)
      - Smyth (Box 67a, Folder 3)
      - Spotsylvania (Box 67a, Folder 4)
      - Warren (Box 67a, Folder 5)
      - Washington (Box 67a, Folder 6)
      - Wise (Box 67a, Folder 7)
      - Wythe (Box 67a, Folder 8)
      - York (Box 67a, Folder 9)
      - Bristol (Box 67a, Folder 10)
      - Clifton Forge (Box 67a, Folder 11)
      - Covington (Box 67a, Folder 12)
      - Fredericksburg (Box 67a, Folder 13)
      - Hampton (Box 67a, Folder 14)
      - Harrisonburg (Box 67a, Folder 15)
      - Lexington (Box 67a, Folder 16)
      - Lynchburg (Box 67a, Folder 17)
      - Martinsville (Box 67a, Folder 18)
      - Newport News (Box 67a, Folder 19)
      - Norfolk (Box 67a, Folder 20)
      - Petersburg (Box 67a, Folder 21)
      - Radford (Box 67a, Folder 22)
      - Richmond (Box 67a, Folder 23)
      - Roanoke (Box 67a, Folder 24)
      - South Boston (Box 67a, Folder 25)
      - Staunton (Box 67a, Folder 26)
      - Williamsburg (Box 67a, Folder 27)
      - Winchester (Box 67a, Folder 28)
    - 1968-1970
      - Albemarle (Box 67b, Folder 1)
      - Albemarle (Box 67b, Folder 2)
      - Appomattox (Box 67b, Folder 3)
      - Botetourt (Box 67b, Folder 4)
      - Charlotte (Box 67b, Folder 5)
      - Craig (Box 67b, Folder 6)
      - Culpeper (Box 67b, Folder 7)
      - Dinwiddie (Box 67b, Folder 8)
      - Fairfax (Box 67b, Folder 9)
      - Fauquier (Box 67b, Folder 10)
      - Floyd (Box 67b, Folder 11)
      - Giles (Box 67b, Folder 12)
      - Goochland (Box 67b, Folder 13)
      - Grayson (Box 67b, Folder 14)
      - Greene (Box 67b, Folder 15)
      - Halifax (Box 67b, Folder 16)
      - Hanover (Box 67b, Folder 17)
      - Isle of Wight (Box 67b, Folder 18)
      - King William (Box 67b, Folder 19)
      - Lee (Box 67b, Folder 20)
      - Loudoun (Box 67b, Folder 21)
      - Madison (Box 67b, Folder 22)
      - Mecklenburg (Box 67b, Folder 23)
      - Montgomery (Box 67b, Folder 24)
      - Nelson (Box 67b, Folder 25)
      - Northumberland (Box 67b, Folder 26)
      - Nottoway (Box 67b, Folder 27)
      - Orange (Box 67b, Folder 28)
      - Patrick (Box 67b, Folder 29)
      - Pittsylvania (Box 67b, Folder 30)
      - Prince Edward (Box 67b, Folder 31)
      - Prince George (Box 67b, Folder 32)
      - Prince William (Box 67b, Folder 33)
      - Pulaski (Box 67b, Folder 34)
      - Roanoke (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Scott (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Shenandoah (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Smyth (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Spotsylvania (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Warren (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Washington (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Wise (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Wythe (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - York (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Bristol (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Covington (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Fredericksburg (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Hampton (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Harrisonburg (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Lynchburg (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - Martinsville (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - Newport News (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - Norfolk (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - Petersburg (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - Portsmouth (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - Radford (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - Richmond (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - Roanoke (Box 68, Folder 24)
      - Staunton (Box 68, Folder 25)
      - Vinton (Box 68, Folder 26)
      - Williamsburg (Box 68, Folder 27)
      - Winchester (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - 1970-1972
      - Accomack (Box 68, Folder 29)
      - Albemarle (Box 68, Folder 30)
      - Appomattox (Box 68, Folder 31)
      - Botetourt (Box 68, Folder 32)
      - Craig (Box 68, Folder 33)
      - Culpeper (Box 68, Folder 34)
      - Dinwiddie (Box 68, Folder 35)
      - Fairfax (Box 68, Folder 36)
      - Fauquier (Box 68, Folder 37)
      - Floyd (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Giles (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Goochland (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Grayson (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Greene (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Halifax (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Hanover (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Isle of Wight (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Lee (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Loudoun (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Madison (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Mecklenburg (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Montgomery (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Nelson (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Nottoway (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - Orange (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - Patrick (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - Pittsylvania (Box 69, Folder 18)
      - Prince Edward (Box 69, Folder 19)
      - Prince George (Box 69, Folder 20)
      - Prince William (Box 69, Folder 21)
      - Pulaski (Box 69, Folder 22)
      - Roanoke (Box 69, Folder 23)
      - Scott (Box 69, Folder 24)
      - Shenandoah (Box 69, Folder 25)
      - Smyth (Box 69, Folder 26)
      - Spotsylvania (Box 69, Folder 27)
      - Warren (Box 69, Folder 28)
      - Washington (Box 69, Folder 29)
      - Wise (Box 69, Folder 30)
      - Wythe (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - York (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Bristol (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Clifton Forge (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Covington (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Fredericksburg (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Hampton (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Harrisonburg (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Lynchburg (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Martinsville (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Newport News (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Norfolk (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Petersburg (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Portsmouth (Box 70, Folder 14)
      - Radford (Box 70, Folder 15)
      - Richmond (Box 70, Folder 16)
      - Roanoke (Box 70, Folder 17)
      - Staunton (Box 70, Folder 18)
      - Vinton (Box 70, Folder 19)
      - Williamsburg (Box 70, Folder 20)
      - Winchester (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - 1972-1974
      - Accomack (Box 70, Folder 22)
      - Albemarle (Box 70, Folder 23)
      - Amelia (Box 70, Folder 24)
      - Appomattox (Box 70, Folder 25)
      - Botetourt (Box 70, Folder 26)
      - Culpeper (Box 70, Folder 27)
      - Dinwiddie (Box 70, Folder 28)
      - Fairfax (Box 70, Folder 29)
      - Fauquier (Box 70, Folder 30)
      - Floyd (Box 70, Folder 31)
      - Giles (Box 70, Folder 32)
      - Goochland (Box 70, Folder 33)
      - Grayson (Box 70, Folder 34)
      - Greene (Box 70, Folder 35)
      - Halifax (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Hanover (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Isle of Wight (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Lee (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Loudoun (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Madison (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Mecklenburg (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Montgomery (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Nelson (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Orange (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Patrick (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Pittsylvania (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Prince Edward (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Prince George (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - Prince William (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Pulaski (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - Roanoke (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - Scott (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - Shenandoah (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - Smyth (Box 71, Folder 20)
      - Spotsylvania (Box 71, Folder 21)
      - Warren (Box 71, Folder 22)
      - Washington (Box 71, Folder 23)
      - Wise (Box 71, Folder 24)
      - Wythe (Box 71, Folder 25)
      - York (Box 71, Folder 26)
      - Alexandria (Box 71, Folder 27)
      - Bristol (Box 71, Folder 28)
      - Clifton Forge (Box 71, Folder 29)
      - Covington (Box 71, Folder 30)
      - Fredericksburg (Box 71, Folder 31)
      - Hampton (Box 71, Folder 32)
      - Harrisonburg (Box 71, Folder 33)
      - Lynchburg (Box 71, Folder 34)
      - Martinsville (Box 71, Folder 35)
      - Newport News (Box 71, Folder 36)
      - Norfolk (Box 71, Folder 37)
      - Petersburg (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Portsmouth (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Radford (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Richmond (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Roanoke (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Staunton (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Vinton (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Williamsburg (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Winchester (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Reports of Expenses
    - 1946
      - Abingdon-Front Royal (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Gate City-Louisa (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Madison-York (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - 1947
      - Abingdon-Fredericksburg (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Gate City-Orange (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Patrick-York (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - 1948
      - Abingdon-Louisa (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Madison-York (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 1949
      - Abingdon-Giles (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Glade Creek-Pulaski (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Radford-York (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 1950
      - Albemarle-Front Royal (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Gate City-Pulaski (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Radford-York (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - 1951
      - Abingdon-Grayson (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Hampton-Staunton (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Tazewell-York (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - 1952
      - Abingdon-Grayson (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Hampton-York (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - 1953
      - Abingdon-Grayson (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Hampton-Yuma Wolfe Cemetery (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - 1954
      - Abingdon-Grayson (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Hampton-Yellow Tavern (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - 1955
      - Abingdon-Huguenot Springs (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Isle of Wight-York (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - 1956
      - Abingdon-Grayson (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Hampton-York (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - 1960
      - Abingdon-Lynchburg (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Madison-Yellow Tavern (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Series V: Correspondence, 1921-1977., Extent: 32 boxes. (Box 78-102.)
  The Correspondence series is housed in twenty-five boxes and is arranged in five subseries. Subseries have been designated for the Confederate Pension Administrator, Deceased Daughters, Deceased Widows, Incoming Correspondence, and Pension Clerk's Correspondence. This series includes mostly correspondence, but also pension applications, invoices, notification cards, death certificates, obituaries, forms, and other sundry items. All five subseries relate to the general administration of Confederate pensions, especially those awarded to the widows or daughters of Confederate veterans. The chief value of this series is in the genealogical information it provides on veterans, their wives, and those daughters who were eligible to receive a pension. Note that there is a large gap from 1926 to 1959 without administrative correspondence. Please consult the Confederate Memorial Association & Funeral Expenses series for records during this time period.
  Arranged into five subseries.
  - Subseries A: Confederate Pension Administrator, 1963-1977., Extent: 11 boxes. (Box 78-88.)
    The Confederate Pension Administrator subseries is housed in eleven archival boxes and is arranged in chronological order, then alphabetically by subject. This subseries contains both incoming & outgoing correspondence from Maxie Duty, Confederate Pension Administrator, until her retirement on 2 September 1970. Duty was succeeded by Nancy W. Stoll, Staff Assistant. The correspondence in this subseries relates to requests of daughters of Confederate veterans to be placed on the pension list, requests for changes of address, requests for genealogical information about veterans, requests for duplicate checks for payment, and missing or late pension payments. Correspondence originates from Ryland H. Ford, Deputy Treasurer, regarding stopped payments, Frank B. Miller, Jr., Assistant Treasurer, regarding returned pensions, and William M. Tuck, Congress, regarding constituent inquiries. The correspondence often includes bonds for duplicate warrants from the Department of Accounts and sometimes includes an application for pension.
    The alphabetical files relate to the applications disapproved, eligibility letters, stopped payments, returned checks, correspondence with organizations including the Sons of Confederate Veterans and the Virginia Division of the United Daughters of the Confederacy, and other sundry items. The Applications Disapproved file includes correspondence from Maxie Duty, applications, & certificates of the State Library regarding Civil War service. This file also includes correspondence from the pension applicant. The Eligibility Letters files include correspondence from Nancy Stoll, Staff Assistant, regarding pensioner's eligibility or potential eligibility to receive a pension. Only widows of Confederate veterans or daughters of veterans who were maidens or widows and whose income did not exceed ninety dollars per month were eligible to receive a pension. This file also contains applications and certificates issued by the Virginia State Library. The Payments Stopped files contains correspondence from pensioners regarding lost checks, stop payment orders issued by the Confederate Pension Administrator, correspondence from Ryland H. Ford, Deputy Treasurer, concerning stopped payments on pension checks, and correspondence from Nancy Stoll requesting duplicate checks. The Checks Returned files include form no. 58 and are arranged alphabetically by pensioner (see Daughter Enrolled subseries).The Sons of Confederate Veterans file contains correspondence from Maxie Duty to A. Frankland Brandt, Administrator of Confederate Dependents, regarding statistics on pensioners, statements of cash receipts & disbursements of the Sons of Confederate Veterans, minutes of the 68th General Convention in 1963, and a report of the Adjutant-in-Chief. Also noteworthy are statistical reports which provide the number of widows on the pension roll and the amount each pensioner receives each month. Lastly, there are files devoted to several presidents of the Virginia Division of the United Daughters of the Confederacy including Margaret S. Palmer, F.B. Fitzgerald, Alice W. Jones, Harriett H. Armentrout, and Mrs. Fred L. Bower, Sr. Palmer's file includes lists of pensioners, their roll number, age, and ancestor as approved by the UDC and sent to the State Comptroller's Office.
    Arranged chronologically, then alphabetically.
    - 1963-1964
      - A-B (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - C-D (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - E-H (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - J-O (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - P-S (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - T-Z (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - 1965-1966
      - A-B (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - C-D (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - E-G (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - H-K (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - L-O (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - P-S (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - T-Z (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 1966-1967
      - A-Bl (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Bo-Bu (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - C (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - D-E (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - F-Go (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Gr-He (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Hi-K (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - L-Mc (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Me-O (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - P-Ra (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Re-Si (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Sl-Te (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Th-We (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Wh-Z (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - 1967-1968
      - A-B (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - C-E (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - F-H (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - J-O (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - P-Sh (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Si-T (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - W-Z (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - 1969-1970
      - A-C (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - D-K (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - L-P (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - R-Z (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - 1971-1972
      - A-L (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - M-Y (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - 1973-1974
      - A-R (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - S-W (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Applications Disapproved, 1967-1977 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Armentrout, Hariette H., 1963-1965 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Bower, Mrs. Fred L., n.d. (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Change of Address, 1964-1977 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Checks Returned
      - 1968-1970 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - 1970-1972 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - 1972-1978
        - A-G (Box 86, Folder 7)
        - H-R (Box 86, Folder 8)
        - S-Y (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Craghead, Mrs. W. Warren, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Date of Death Pending, 1964-1970 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Death Notices/Change of Address, 1960-1961 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Eligibility Letters
      - 1951-1970 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - 1971-1974 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - 1977 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Fitzgerald, Mrs. F.B., 1969-1973 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Jones, Alice W., 1960-1961 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965-1978 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Overby, Archer H., 1963-1965 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Palmer, Margaret S., 1973-1976 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Payments Stopped
      - 1970 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - 1973-1978 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Returned Checks, 1974-1977 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Roberts, David E., 1960-1961 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Sons of Confederate Veterans, 1963-1966 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Statistical Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Sydnor, Mrs. Walter, Jr., 1961-1963 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Deceased Daughters, 1965-1977., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 89-91.)